https://www.regaltent.com/privacy-policy/

Your Privacy Is Important To Us
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.regaltent.com/. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship machinery.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email at sales@regaltent.com or by calling 1-800-364-4430See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Cookies We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in with a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.Links This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email at sales@regaltent.com or by calling 1-800-364-4430 Terms and Conditions for the www.regaltent.com WebsiteIntroductionThese Terms and Conditions (“Terms”, “Terms and Conditions”) govern your relationship with www.regaltent.com/ website (the “Website”) operated by Regal Tents and Structures.Please read these Terms and Conditions carefully before using the Website.Your access to and use of the Website is based on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Website.By accessing or using the Website you agree to be bound by these Terms and accept all legal consequences. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, in whole or in part, please do not use the Website.Intellectual Property RightsOther than the content you own, under these Terms, Regal Tents and Structures and/or its licensors own all the intellectual property rights and materials contained in the Website.The Website and all contents, including but not limited to text, images, graphics or code are the property of Regal Tents and Structures and are protected by copyright, trademarks, database and other intellectual property rights. You may display and copy, download or print portions of the material from the different areas of the Website only for your own non-commercial use, or to place an order with Regal Tents and Structures. Any other use is strictly prohibited and may violate copyright, trademark and other laws. These Terms do not grant you a license to use any trademark of Regal Tents and Structures or its affiliates. You further agree not to use, change or delete any proprietary notices from materials downloaded from the Website.RestrictionsYou are specifically restricted from all of the following:       publishing any www.regaltent.com/ material in any other media;       selling, sublicensing and/or otherwise commercializing any www.regaltent.com/ material;       publicly performing and/or showing any www.regaltent.com/ material;       using www.regaltent.com/ in any way that is or may be damaging to the Website;       using www.regaltent.com/ in any way that impacts user access to the Website;       using www.regaltent.com/ contrary to applicable laws and regulations, or in any way may cause harm to the Website, or to any person or business entity;       engaging in any data mining, data harvesting, data extracting or any other similar activity in relation to the Website;       using the Website to engage in any advertising or marketing.Certain areas of the Website are restricted from being accessed by you and www.regaltent.com/ may further restrict access by you to any areas of the Website, at any time, in absolute discretion.Availability, Errors and InaccuraciesIn order to provide exceptional service and accuracy, we regularly update the products and services on the Website.We cannot and do not guarantee the accuracy or completeness of any information, including prices, product images, specifications, availability, and services. We reserve the right to change or update information and to correct errors, inaccuracies, or omissions at any time without prior notice.Despite our best efforts, the products or services available on our Website may have an error regarding the price, be inaccurately described, or be unavailable.We may experience delays in updating information on the Website and in our advertising on other websites.Links To Other Web SitesThe Website may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by www.regaltent.com/.Regal Tents and Structures has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that Regal Tents and Structures shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such websites or services.We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party web sites or services that you visit.IndemnificationYou agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Regal Tents and Structures, its principals, officers, directors, representatives, employees, contractors, licensors, licensees, suppliers and agents, from and against any claims, losses, damages, losses, obligations, costs, actions or demands.These include but are not limited to: (a) legal and accounting fees resulting from your use of the Website; (b) your breach of any of these Terms; (c) anything you post on or upload to the Website; and (d) any activity related to your account. This includes any negligent or illegal conduct by you, any person or entity accessing the Website using your account whether such access is obtained via fraudulent or illegal means.Limitation Of LiabilityRegal Tents and Structures, its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, shall not be liable for any loss or damage, direct or indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, economic loss, loss or damage to electronic media or data, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of the Website; (ii) your inability to access or use the Website; (iii) any conduct or content of any third-party on or related to the Website; (iiv) any content obtained from or through the Website; and (v) the unauthorized access to, use of or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other claim in law, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.Disclaimer And Non-Waiver of RightsRegal Tents and Structures makes no guarantees, representations or warranties of any kind as regards the website and associated technology. Any purportedly applicable warranties, terms and conditions are excluded, to the fullest extent permitted by law. Your use of the Website is at your sole risk. The Website is provided on an “AS IS” and “AS AVAILABLE” basis. The Website is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance, except as provided for under the laws of any province in Canada. In such cases, the provincial law shall apply to the extent necessary.Regal Tents and Structures and its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Website will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Website is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Website will meet your requirements.If you breach any of these Terms and Regal Tents and Structures chooses not to immediately act, or chooses not to act at all, Regal Tents and Structures will still be entitled to all rights and remedies at any later date, or in any other situation, where you breach these Terms. Regal Tents and Structures does not waive any of its rights. Regal Tents and Structures shall not be responsible for any purported breach of these Terms caused by circumstances beyond its control. A person who is not a party to these Terms shall have no rights of enforcement.You may not assign, sub-license or otherwise transfer any of your rights under these Terms.ExclusionsAs set out, above, some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, so the limitations above may not apply to you. Provincial laws of Canada may apply to certain products and service provided.AssignmentRegal Tents and Structures is allowed to assign, transfer, and subcontract its rights and/or obligations under these Terms without any notification. However, you are not allowed to assign, transfer, or subcontract any of your rights and/or obligations under these Terms.Governing LawThese Terms shall be governed by, and interpreted and enforced in accordance with, the laws in the Province of British Columbia and the laws of Canada, as applicable.If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, then any remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Website, and supersede and replace any prior agreements, oral or otherwise, regarding the Website.ChangesWe reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. By using this Website you are expected to review these Terms on a regular basis.By continuing to access or use our Website after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, in whole or in part, please stop using the Website.Contact UsIf you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.TerminationWe may terminate or suspend access to our Website immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including, without limitation, if you breach the Terms.All provisions of the Terms shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.Upon termination, your right to use the Website will immediately cease. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Website.
Home
Special Event Tents & Floors
Industrial Structures
Professional Services
Portfolio
Blog
Get a Quote
Contact
Subscribe below to stay tuned for news and latest updates.
© 2020 Regal Tent Productions | Privacy & Terms of Use | Website by Loomo
We use cookies to improve your experience on our site. To find out more, please read our Privacy Policy.OkPrivacy policy
